fashion71.net 2016-11-30

# Privacy & Security_Policies_Wholesale clothing, Wholesale Clothes Online From China

At first, our target is to make your shopping experience safe, convenient and care-free. Our privacy and security programs make sure that every transaction made at is 100% safe and guaranteed.

What Information Do We Collect? The types of personal information that we collect from you will depend on the circumstances of collection and on the type of service you request from us. For example, when you wish to purchase a product from we may collect details such as your name, address, delivery address and billing address，and other information relevant to your purchase.

As we are required by law to obtain your consent to the collection of "sensitive information", we will assume that you have given consent to the collection of all information you have provided to us for use in accordance with this Statement, unless you tell us otherwise.

How We Collect Information? We may collect personal information about you when you visit our website, when you deal with us over the Email, we will not collect any personal information without your consent. We consider that your consent is granted when you complete the fields necessary to facilitate a transaction through .

How We Use Your Personal Information We generally collect your personal information for the following purposes:

To facilitate your access to our website, products and services

To deliver products you have ordered from us

To seek your opinion on our products, services, marketing and website.

Some of the personal information we collect is essential for us to be able to accurately identify who is using the service. Other types of personal information we collect help us to develop a profile of who is using our service, this assists us in offering products to suit the needs of the users of .

Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties We may disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose for which the information was collected or for related purposes, for example to complete a transaction on your behalf or provide you with a product that you purchased. We engage third party contractors to perform services for us which involves the contractor handling personal information we hold. For example, we currently engage third party contractors to:

Deliver products purchased from

Provide electronic funds transfer services, credit card account processing and related services

In these situations, the third party contractor is strictly from using any prohibited personal information about you except for the specific purpose for which we have supplied. We may also disclose your personal information to various law enforcement agencies and governments around the world for security, customs and immigration purposes. Other than the above, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorized or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate a suspected unlawful activity.

Security of Your Personal Information We will securely hold your personal information and we will not trade, rent or sell it. We will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you. Personal information may be stored both electronically on our computer system, Firewalls, passwords, anti-virus software and email filters can protect all our electronic information.

Resolving Your Concerns If you wish to gain access to your personal information, have a complaint about a breach of your privacy or you have any query on how your personal information is collected or used please forward your request, complaint or query to the address below. We will respond to your query or complaint via Email as soon as possible.

Changes to This Privacy Statement We may amend this Privacy Statement as our business requirements or the law changes. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will be updated on , so please visit this page periodically to ensure that you have our most current privacy statement.

Note:

1\. Direct Marketing

Fashion71.net Company Ltd. may contact you from time to time with a view to providing the latest information on our products and services / member program. If you do not wish to receive these updates, please login at http://www.fashion71.net to unsubscribe. Alternatively, you may click the unsubscribe link as shown in our electronic promotional materials; or can write to us via e-mail to admin@fashion71.net or via mail at Jia He Industrial District, Baiyun District, Guangzhou City, Guangdong Provice China or via fax to +8620-87247061. In accordance with the statutory requirements, Fashion71.net Company Ltd. will honour your request not to use your Personal Data for the purposes of direct marketing. Unless otherwise instructed as per the above, Fashion71 Company Ltd. may use any of your Personal Data collected in the normal course of our business for direct marketing purposes.

2\. Accessing Personal Data

You have full control and ability to correct or edit your Personal Data at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about direct marketing purpose, VIP promotional offers and new products and services or deletion of your VIP membership online account. You may request your right of access or right of correction by logging in at http://www.fashion71.net. Alternatively, you can write to us via e-mail to admin@fashion71.net or via mail at Jia He Industrial District, Baiyun District, Guangzhou City, Guangdong Provice China or via fax to +8620-87247061. Fashion71 Company Ltd. will, upon satisfying itself of the authenticity and validity of the access or correction request, make every endeavor to comply with and respond to the request within the period set by the statutory requirement.
